Daniel Corbi Boldrin

System Analyst Developer / Game Programmer

Toronto, ON, M6K 2G4 daniel_cboldrin@hotmail.com +1(416)876-2689

Highly focused software analyst and developer with 9 years of experience in a variety of development positions and projects.

I am organized, methodical, and have a keen eye for detailed results and solid coding in trustworthy business software, games, and apps.

I am very creative with visual and analytical problem-solving skills and I have broad experience with leadership of cross-functional teams of technical and non-technical personnel.

Experienced with software specification, requirements, and design.

Work Experience

Game Programming Teacher

Wells Academy - Toronto, ON – Canada February 2021 to Present

Responsible for planning, organizing, and teaching game programming and web development remote classes with Unity3D and C# for class sizes of 6 students from grade 6 to 12. Recognized for teaching and course coordination excellence.

Game Programming Teacher

Thinnox - Mississauga, ON - Canada June 2018 to December 2020

Planned, organized, and taught programming, 3D animation, modeling, circuit, and game design classes for class sizes of 12 students from grade 6 to 12. Recognized for teaching excellence and instructional reports to student's parents.

Analyst Developer

Programmers - Matão, São Paulo - Brazil April 2016 to April 2017

Led a development team responsible for back and front-end programming of an automated medical survey system used over EUA.

Responsible for database management and software architecture using MVC5. Survey collected feedback via 30 online questions to be answered by patients after their visit.

Full Stack Developer

GRX - Araraquara, São Paulo - Brazil March 2016 to January 2017

Being the first point of contact for database improvements and management. Implemented and fixed features in marketing and business software using WAMP and LAMP. Focused on performance improvement.

Analyst Developer

Hewlett Packard - Araraquara, São Paulo - Brazil July 2015 to July 2016

Worked in a contingency team responsible for managing, monitoring, testing, and sustaining all 5 main systems fully functional. Experience with database jobs, bank applications, web pages, automatic emailing, and interactive voice response.

Analyst Developer

Cast Group - Araraquara, São Paulo - Brazil November 2014 to July 2015

Worked in a development team responsible for back and front-end programming of a governmental tax exemption application for flood victims in Brazil.

Responsible for designing and implementing the tax exemption calculation API using C#, MVC5, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, and jQuery.

Full Stack Developer

Líder Telecom - Araraquara, São Paulo — Brazil April 2013 to November 2014

Led a small team in various internal projects for the company, improving the quality of the calls answered by the telecom operators and overall work quality of employees.

Released applications that were used by 3000+ employees.

Developed databases and servers with several automatic routines. Experience with WAMP, LAMP, C# MVC, Aheeva, Active Directory, SQL, IIS.

Education

Game Programming - Diploma

George Brown College - Toronto, ON - Canada Graduated in April 2021

System Analysis and Development - Diploma

Federal Institute of São Paulo - Araraquara, SP - Brazil

Graduated in January 2017

Skills

- Back-End: C# / C++ / C / Python / PHP / Java
- Front-End: HTML / CSS / Javascript / jQuery / Kendo / AngularJS / React JS
- Database and Servers: SQL / MYSQL / IIS / Apache / Linux / Windows
- Game Engines: Unity3D / Unreal Engine / Construct / Scratch / Alice
- Versioning and revision control: GitHub / Perforce / SVN / Tortoise
- Frameworks: XNA / Zend
- Collaboration tools and websites: Slack / Trello / ClickUp / Repl.it / Tinkercad
- Arts: Photoshop / Blender / 3ds Max / Maya / Houdini / Realistic and Technical Drawing
- Other: Team leadership / Gameplay Programming / Prototyping / Agile development / Classroom management / Teaching / System Affordance

Online Portfolio

